yes okay jai ho my subtle and we've spent a lot of
是的，好的，我很细微，我们花了很多时间
time talking about metropolis checking and this presentation
时间谈论大都市检查和此演示文稿
and straight edge where god bless and so shang king
上帝保佑的直边，所以尚王
oh god that's more pretty much all kinds of streams want to be sent to better and
哦，天哪，几乎所有类型的流都希望被发送到更好的位置，
then i'll put back together your slice is teach and share things from
然后我会把你的部分归纳起来
The for shot another positive audible disadvantage is during opponents
射门的另一个积极的可听见的缺点是在对手中
documentary dates are typically yes so on
记录日期通常是，依此类推
wiseguy hobby cooks already the presentation for our stay moment
wiseguy爱好厨师已经为我们的停留时刻做了介绍
different ways to check the same that for those sailing tanks of reasons
检查那些帆船的原因的不同方法相同
sam breakfast block alignment you well within their fling dated as a layman
萨姆早餐块使您在他们作为外行约会时的对齐范围内
target stuff like arno sharding automatic collection of the
目标资料，例如arno分片的自动收集
salon fire bloxam gets narrower blog simon fletcher blogs his mouth the pony
沙龙火bloxam变得更窄博客simon fletcher博客他的嘴小马
and or December when I slept like that
和或者当我这样睡觉时的十二月
the solutions are blocked by der kemp to six no pico studies button, so let's hear it
解决方案被der kemp限制为六个无微微学习按钮，所以让我们听听吧
mexlite
墨西哥陨石
bacon
培根
ankie
安基
yes come trial my neck spy cam princess well and so it is not so finally
是的，可以很好地试用我的脖子间谍cam公主，所以最终并非如此
a process no reviews wars network some details p6 know
一个过程没有评论战争网络一些细节p6知道
if your goal ipad as a killer for example always so on and and the site starts
如果您将ipad当作杀手，例如目标总是如此，并且该网站开始了
here that all on the web so goes the sepia again what i want you [ __ ]
在这里，所有在网络上，所以棕褐色再次去了我想要你拉屎
the inquit bypass sorry this will actually use only for magic and retracted
难道绕过抱歉，这实际上仅用于魔术和撤回
the file and 2 give checker for heading and also a file
该文件和2给标题检查器，还有一个文件
file wtfs and en tools ships and to the wonderful
文件wtfs和en tools随船而来
and the necks wear out the ideal to working groups
脖子磨破了工作组的理想选择
there is a and also a coach and guide to trolling use case ow and
还有一个指导和拖钓用例的教练，以及
so the sides must be between our fiber you like henk and two turtle
所以侧面必须在我们喜欢的纤维和两只乌龟之间
can also still be between the genius of batman dato
仍然可以在蝙蝠侠拿督的天才之间
here on like my busy per party you so how to mouth give the go2 goal
在这里就像我每聚会忙碌的一样，所以如何给go2目标定口
from john field
从约翰·菲尔德
[Applause]
[掌声]